doogee.cc 2018-03-28

# Privacy | Doogee Mobile

DOOGEE is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We do not use, store or disclose your information in ways other than those outlined in this Privacy Policy. To better serve you, we may collect information that can be used to identify you. We will not use that information in ways other than laid out in this document. DOOGEE reserves the right to change or modify this document at any time. Please let us know if you have any questions.

**The information we collect and how it is used**

In order to better serve you, we collect both personal and non-personal information. The information we collect may include your name, email address, postal address and phone number. Your information may be used in the following ways:

When you visit our website, your IP address' geolocation data is used to present you with the most relevant currency and shipping options.

When you subscribe to the DOOGEE newsletter, we collect your email to send you news and promotions.

When you create a DOOGEE Account, we collect your name and email to validate your account and send you notifications.

When you participate in our promotions or order products from the DOOGEE website, we collect your postal address and telephone number for logistical purposes.

When we ship your order, your postal address will be given to our logistics partners to facilitate delivery.

**Managing your personal information**

We may occasionally send you news on our products and promotions. If you wish to unsubscribe you may do so in your DOOGEE Account. You may also modify your information by updating your profile or by sending us a request to [sales-support@doogee.cc](http://mailto:sales-support@doogee.cc/)

**Disclosure to third parties**

We share relevant information with various third-party businesses so that they may provide us with services such as email, website analytics, targeted promotions, payment processing, order processing and delivery. Third party partners are also obligated to protect your privacy and never receive your full account information.

In order to optimize your user experience, DOOGEE uses third-party service providers that offer certain analytics and user interaction services in connection with our website. These services include the collection and tracking of certain data and information regarding the characteristics and activities of visitors to this site. We may disclose Visitor data, including Personally Identifiable Information, to certain such providers in order to obtain these services.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data sent from web servers that are stored on your device. We use cookies to remember your preferences and facilitate online shopping. You may disable cookies in your browser if you do not wish to accept them.

**Children's privacy**

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not knowingly collect information from children under 13.

**Location-based Services**

In order to better provide recommendations, navigation, weather and other related services, DOOGEE may collect, use and share with partners relevant information regarding the real-time location of your DOOGEE device or online login. This information will be collected anonymously.

**Information security**

We use industry standard security measures to ensure your personal information is safe. Payments on DOOGEE.net are handled by PayPal and transmitted using the Secure Sockets Layer protocol (SSL) with 2048-bit encryption. DOOGEE does not store or have access to your payment details. Your credit/debit card information is retained via PayPal’s or Yandex’s servers.

**Third Party Policies**

DOOGEE’ website and devices may contain links and services offered by third parties. For example, online purchases are handled via PayPal. Android also uses a suite of applications provided by Google. Information collected by such third parties is governed by their own privacy and legal policies.

**Commitment to Privacy**

At DOOGEE, we take your privacy very seriously. If you have any questions regarding privacy or would like to make a complaint regarding a privacy breach, please feel free to contact us. We may periodically update our Privacy Policy. When we update our Privacy Policy, we will post the most recent date on which the policy was updated.

**Email:  **[sales-support@doogee.cc](http://mailto:sales-support@doogee.cc/)
